# CÉSAR GARCÍA CABEZA

## **Software Engineer graduate**

- @ cesar.gar.cabeza@gmail.com themrcesi in cesargarciacabeza
  - **J** +34 648035992
- Pola de Siero, Spain
- themrcesi.github.io

# **EDUCATION**

## M.Sc. in Artificial Intelligence

#### **Technical University of Madrid**

- September 2020 Present
- Madrid, Spain

#### B.Sc. in Computer Science

#### Wroclaw University of Science & Technology

**2018 - 2019** 

- Wroclaw, Poland
- Erasmus exchange during the academic course 2018/2019.

# B.Eng. in Computer Software Engineering

## **University of Oviedo**

**2016 - 2020** 

- Oviedo, Spain
- Coursed 204 ECTS in English.
- Average grade: 8.33 (out of 10).

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Software Engineer Intern

#### **DAIL Software**

April 2021 - Present

#### Research Intern

#### **Biomedical Informatics Group, Technical University of Madrid**

September 2020 - September 2020

#### Undergraduate Research Intern

## **UNIMODE** Research Group, University of Oviedo

September 2019 - October 2019

Oviedo, Spain

The following tasks were performed in collaboration with two professors of the Computation and Artificial Intelligence department:

- Analysis and optimization of algorithms.
- Development of algorithms.

The previous tasks were applied to a specific problem: aggregation of partially ordered sets. This work set a baseline for my Final Degree Project, obtaining later a grade of 10.

# LIFE PHILOSOPHY

" Always ready to learn new things. If I have a goal, I don't stop until I get it."

# ABOUT ME

Software engineer graduate with a passion for technology and artificial intelligence especially machine and deep learning and its real-life applications such as natural language processing.

I am a passionate lover of sports, having played: football, basketball, volleyball, tennis, panel, fronton, badminton, snowboard... But, without any doubt, Judo is, and will always be, my real passion. Judo has been present in my life since I was 6 years old, and nowadays I have the black belt, 2° DAN. Thanks to this incredible sport I have learnt essential values such as respect, self control, perseverance and overcoming.

# STRENGTHS

Motivator & Leader | Curious

Hard-working

Problem solving

Ability to work in team

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Software Design & Development

**Computer Vision** 

Information Retrieval

Machine and Deep Learning

Web Scrapping

Agile Methods

NLP

Docker

Pvthon

React

# **SCHOLARSHIPS**

### **Erasmus+ Grant**

## **University of Oviedo**

**September 2018 - June 2019** 

Oviedo, Spain

## **Excellent Academic Achievement Scholarship**

## **University of Oviedo**

**September 2016 - June 2017** 

Oviedo, Spain

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Deep Learning Specialization

#### Coursera

**■** January 2021

Skills: Neural Networks, Convolutional Neural Networks, Recurrent Neural Networks, Keras, Tensorflow.

# Machine Learning, Data Science and Deep Learning with Python **Udemy**

August 2020

Skills: Python, Numpy, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Machine Learning, Recommender Systems, Neural Networks.

# **COURSES**

#### First-Aid

## Cruz Roja

**March** 2014 - May 2014

# **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

#### Volunteer

#### **Erasmus Student Network Oviedo**

**September 2019 - Present** 

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish English French



C1 Advanced

## **Cambridge Assesment English**

**=** 2017

Delf B1

## **Alliance Française**

**=** 2015